<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-08-27T09:52:10-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Seiji Shaw</title><subtitle>EECS PhD Student, MIT&lt;br /&gt;seijis [at] mit [dot] edu&lt;br /&gt;Office: 45-633</subtitle><author><name>Seiji Shaw</name></author><entry><title type="html">A Blog?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2023/03/28/first-post.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Blog?" /><published>2023-03-28T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-03-28T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2023/03/28/first-post</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2023/03/28/first-post.html">&lt;p&gt;Hello! Welcome to the new blog section of my website. 
This is a place for ramblings, thoughtlets, rants, and other odd bits. 
I added some nice Ghibli banners to counterbalance the chaos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To be frank, the blog is still under construction. There are lots of things to add –
a commenting mechanism, MathJax… all that good stuff. Except I accidentally pushed the branch… and now it’s too late.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To set some expectations: I won’t be posting very frequently – probably when
the spirit of the Aibishter moves me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See you all for the first (official) post (probably when I’m actually done putting the blog infrastructure together)!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Seiji Shaw</name></author><summary type="html">Hello! Welcome to the new blog section of my website. This is a place for ramblings, thoughtlets, rants, and other odd bits. I added some nice Ghibli banners to counterbalance the chaos. To be frank, the blog is still under construction. There are lots of things to add – a commenting mechanism, MathJax… all that good stuff. Except I accidentally pushed the branch… and now it’s too late. To set some expectations: I won’t be posting very frequently – probably when the spirit of the Aibishter moves me. See you all for the first (official) post (probably when I’m actually done putting the blog infrastructure together)!</summary></entry></feed>